Step 1: click (1231, 496) [OK]\NI can see a Booking.com page with a modal dialog box open that says 'Sign in, save money' with a 'Genius' logo. This dia
Step 2: click (597, 502) [OK]\NI can see the Booking.com homepage with a search form. The task requires me to search for a hotel in Kyoto for 2 adults,
Step 3: click (478, 718) [OK]\NI can see the Booking.com homepage with a search form. There's a dropdown menu showing 'Trending destinations' with seve
Step 4: click (1042, 745) [OK]\NI can see the Booking.com homepage with a calendar modal open showing February 2026 and March 2026. The task requires me
Step 5: click (1042, 793) [OK]\NI can see the Booking.com homepage with a calendar modal open showing February 2026 and March 2026. The destination fiel
Step 6: click (1083, 793) [OK]\NI can see the Booking.com homepage with a calendar modal open showing February 2026 and March 2026. The destination fiel
Step 7: click (1455, 502) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Booking.com homepage with a search form. The destination field shows 'K
Step 8: click (1455, 502) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see the Booking.com homepage with a search form. The destination field shows 'K
Step 9: click (162, 28) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see a browser with two tabs open - one for Booking.com and one showing 'Loading
Step 10: done  [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see a Booking.com search results page for Kyoto. The search has already been pe